herbpathy.com 2019-09-24

# Privacy Policy : Herbpathy

Herbpathy Privacy Policy

**Herbpathy.com** provides the information best available through extensive research. Content cited on this website is purely for informational use and user/visitor should take proper care while using for any kind of health related use.

By accessing herbpathy.com, you agree the terms and conditions regarding the use of information provided by us.

**Privacy Statement :**

It may require the visitor to provide personal information i.e. Name, E-mail address and Date of Birth and similar personal information in order to access services like feedback etc. 

We are fully concern about the security and privacy of the users and do not sell or rent the Personal information. At herbpathy.com, your privacy is our responsibility.

**Use of Personal Information :**

Personal information provided by you may be used ;

• To send time to time updates

• To authenticate the Personal Information provided

• To stop criminal activities

• To investigate illegal activities

**External Links :**

Herbpathy.com may have some links for Google ads or any other third party ads. These ads may be based on reading or placing cookies on your browser. When you click on these links you jump to that website. Once you leave our website, we have no control over the privacy statement or the security of personal information provided there. Moreover, in that case we are not responsible for any kind of information loss.

**Change in Privacy Statement :**

Herbpathy.com reserves all the rights to change or modify the privacy statement as a whole or partially if we feel any need to do so. It may also be due to some changes or modification in the services we provide.

**Queries :**

If you have any concerns regarding this privacy statement, you can write us at **info@herbpathy.com**.
